https://sawbill.com/privacy/

Home / Privacy
Home / Privacy
Sawbill Canoe Outfitters has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our online information gathering and dissemination practices.
Our overall policy is extremely simple: If we collect information from you, we use it only for the purposes for which it was collected, and the other limited purposes outlined below. We will not sell or share your personally identifiable information with any third party (except under the circumstances detailed below).
Here are the details of our privacy policies. This statement may change over time—please review it periodically.
Types of Information Collected; Uses of Information
We collect some non-personally identifiable information automatically and some in our online forms. Non-personally identifiable information might include your IP address, the type of browser or operating system you use, or the domain name from which you linked to our site. We use this non-personally identifiable information to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site.
Our site’s electronic forms may also request or require users to give us personally identifiable information (like their name, telephone number, home address and e-mail address). We may use the information from our registration forms and surveys to contact the user. We will not sell or disclose your personally identifiable data to any third party that is not an affiliate of Sawbill Canoe Outfitters unless: (i) we transfer of our business assets (as further described below); (ii) we first obtain permission from you; (iii) we need to share it with agents or contractors who perform services for us; or (iv) we are required by law to disclose it.
Sawbill Canoe Outfitters uses information for the following general purposes: to fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, and conduct research.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
Sawbill Canoe Outfitters does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:
On rare occasions, we provide the information to trusted noncommercial partners who work with Sawbill Canoe Outfitters under confidentiality agreements. These organizations do not have any independent right to share your information.
We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person or as otherwise required by law.
We transfer information about you if Sawbill Canoe Outfitters is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Sawbill Canoe Outfitters will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
Transfer of Business Assets
As we continue to develop our business, we may be acquired, merge with another business, or acquire or buy other businesses or assets. In such transactions, both personally and non-personally identifiable information will likely be one of the transferred assets.
Cookies
We may use “cookies” to determine whether you have visited our site previously and to save and remember any preferences that you set while using our site. Our cookies cannot retrieve any other data from a hard drive or obtain an e-mail address. Although a user has the ability to modify most browsers to either accept all cookies, notify the user when a cookie is sent, or reject all cookies, it may not be possible to utilize certain services at Sawbill.com if cookies are rejected.
Links
This site contains links to other sites. Sawbill Canoe Outfitters is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Public Forums
This site may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. By posting information, you also give Sawbill Canoe Outfitters the unlimited right to use and republish the information as we see fit.
Security
While there is no such thing as “perfect” security on the Internet, we will take all reasonable steps to ensure the safety of your personally identifiable information. This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. However, we do not assume any liability for third-party usage of your personal information, whether obtained legally or illegally from our system.
Children
Sawbill Canoe Outfitters does not seek to collect any information from children under the age of 13. If any child provides us with personally identifiable information, a parent or guardian may notify us and such information will be deleted from our records.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
